const level7Questions = [
{
        question: "Canh, súp",
        answers: ["蛋 (dàn)", "汤 (tāng)"],
        correct: "汤 (tāng)",
    },
    {
        question: "Những cái này",
        answers: ["这些 (zhèxiē)", "一些 (yìxiē)"],
        correct: "这些 (zhèxiē)",
    },
    {
        question: "Những cái kia",
        answers: ["那些 (nàxiē)", "些 (xiē)"],
        correct: "那些 (nàxiē)",
    },
    {
        question: "Há cảo, sủi cảo",
        answers: ["饺子 (jiǎozi)", "包子 (bāozi)"],
        correct: "饺子 (jiǎozi)",
    },
    {
        question: "Mì, bún, sợi mì",
        answers: ["面条 (miàntiáo)", "玛丽 (Mǎlì)"],
        correct: "面条 (miàntiáo)",
    },
    {
        question: "Bán",
        answers: ["买 (mǎi)", "卖 (mài)"],
        correct: "卖 (mài)",
    },
    {
        question: "Kilogram",
        answers: ["斤 (jīn)", "公斤 (gōngjīn)"],
        correct: "公斤 (gōngjīn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Táo",
        answers: ["水果 (shuǐguǒ)", "苹果 (píngguǒ)"],
        correct: "苹果 (píngguǒ)",
    },
    {
        question: "Đắt, quý",
        answers: ["贵 (guì)", "了 (le)"],
        correct: "贵 (guì)",
    },
    {
        question: "Bao nhiêu",
        answers: ["吧 (ba)", "多少 (duōshǎo)"],
        correct: "多少 (duōshǎo)",
    },
    {
        question: "Nhiều, hơn",
        answers: ["多 (duō)", "少 (shǎo)"],
        correct: "多 (duō)",
    },
    {
        question: "Đồng, tệ",
        answers: ["块 (kuài)", "角 (jiǎo)"],
        correct: "块 (kuài)",
    },
    {
        question: "Hào",
        answers: ["毛 (máo)", "元 (yuán)"],
        correct: "毛 (máo)",
    },
    {
        question: "Xu",
        answers: ["分 (fēn)", "块 (kuài)"],
        correct: "分 (fēn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Vẫn, trả lại",
        answers: ["还 (hái / huán)", "别的 (bié de)"],
        correct: "还 (hái / huán)",
    },
    {
        question: "Khác",
        answers: ["别的 (bié de)", "橘子 (júzi)"],
        correct: "别的 (bié de)",
    },
];

export default level7Questions;
